Men’s Lives Documentation Project Interviews
Archive of Folk Culture, American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
Guides to the Collections in the Archive of Folk Culture
Men’s Lives Documentation Project Interviews 1981-1985
AFC 1998/015
5 linear feet (11 boxes), including 4050 manuscripts, 130 sound recordings, and 2 graphic materials.
Eilertsen, John, interviewer.
manuscripts: 3,025 file cards.
122 sound cassettes: analog.
2 reels microfilm.
6 boxes.
Archive of Folk Culture, American Folklife Center, Library of Congress Washington, D.C.
Original documentation of the history and maritime occupational culture of a small fishing community from South Fork, Long Island, New York.
Selected Search Terms
The following terms have been used to index the description of this collection in the LC Catalog. They are grouped by name of person or organization, by subject or location, and by occupation and listed alphabetically.
People
De Menil, Adelaide; Eilertsen, John; Lester, Stewart
Organizations
Rock Foundation Trust
Subjects
Atlantic menhaden fisheries--Atlantic Coast (U.S.); Eel fisheries--New York (State)--Long Island.; Field recordings--New York (State)--Long Island.; Fishers--New York (State)--Long Island--History.; Fishers--New York (State)--Long Island--Interviews.; Seining--New York (State)--Long Island.
Places
East End (Long Island, N.Y.)--Social life and customs.
Form/Genre
Field recordings.; Interviews (Sound recordings); Oral histories
Arrangement
The collection has been arranged by format into the following series: Manuscripts, Sound Recordings, and Graphic Images. All sound recordings indicated in the donor’s log have been assigned unique AFC ID numbers and the original order of the collection has been retained. For several interviews a transcript is included, but the corresponding sound recording was not received with the collection.
Acquisition
The Men’s Lives Documentation Project collection was acquired by the Library of Congress’ Prints and Photographs Division in 1996. In 1997, the photographs and the oral history interview audio recordings, transcripts, and subject access note cards were separated and the latter were transferred to the Archive of Folk Culture, American Folklife Center.
Access and Restrictions
Collection is open for research. Access to recordings may be restricted. To request materials, please contact the Folklife Reading Room at http://hdl.loc.gov/loc.afc/folklife.contact. Duplication of collection materials may be governed by copyright and other restrictions.
Related Material
Original project photographs (circa 140,000 prints) are located in the Library of Congress, Prints and Photographs Division; unprocessed in PR 13 CN 1996:063.
Publications
Matthiessen, Peter. Men's Lives: The Surfmen and Baymen of the South Fork. New York: Rock Foundation, 1986.
Biographical Notes
The Rock Foundation is a philanthropic institution founded by Adelaide de Menil, a photographer and cultural documentarian. John Eilertsen is a folklorist and was executive director of the Bridgehampton Historical Society at the time of this project.
Scope and Content
The materials in this collection were produced as part of the Men’s Lives project, sponsored by Adelaide de Menil and The Rock Foundation, to document the occupational culture, lifestyle, and heritage of a small fishing community of surfmen and baymen on the East End of Long Island. This collection includes oral history interviews and interview transcripts, notes, and a file card index of interview excerpts, field notes, and subject headings. Related ephemera include a publicity file of English and French language press coverage of the Men’s Lives exhibition.
In 1981, a local fisherman and photographer, Doug Kuntz, expressed the desire to document his local East End community of fishers on South Fork, Long Island, whose traditions can be traced back three hundred years to its original settlement during the seventeenth century. Adelaide de Menil encouraged Kuntz to pursue the project and invited seven other photographers and writer Peter Matthiessen to document the community. The materials gathered during the following four years became the source material for the Men’s Lives traveling exhibition and for Matthiessen’s book Men's Lives: The Surfmen and Baymen of the South Fork (1986).
Between 1981 and 1985, individuals from the fishing community participated in interviews covering all aspects of maritime commercial fishing and included occupational culture, lifestyle, and heritage in their discussions. Family history is particularly well documented in this collection, as multiple members of the Lester and King families were interviewed, many more than once. These interviews were conducted by folklorist John Eilertsen and include the following maritime topics: handlining, gill netting, eeling, dragging, cod fishing, sport fishing, sword fishing, shell fishing, menhaden fishery, long lining, lobster fishing, haul seining, decoys (gunning and trapping), wind weather and tide boats, net mending and rope splicing, whaling, trap fishing, shipping and selling, income and expenses, and legislation and politics.
Collection Concordance by Format
Series I: Manuscripts
105 folders AFC Box 1-6
3,025 note cards AFC Box 8
Series II: Sound Recordings
130 audio cassettes NAVCC
Series III: Graphic Materials
2 rolls of microfilm AFC Box 7
Container List
- Series I: Manuscripts
  - Collection Finding Aid, 16 pages. (Box-folder 1/1)
  - Tape Index and Logs, 96 pages. (Box-folder 1/2)
  - Transcript – Edwards, Joshua B. and Smith, Nat, SR001/A101.; 13 pages. (Box-folder 1/3)
    East Hampton Maritime Folklife.
  - Transcript – Smith, Nat, SR002-SR003/A102-A103.; 26 pages. (Box-folder 1/4)
  - Transcript – Edwards, Captain Jack, SR004-SR005/A104-A105.; 44 pages. (Box-folder 1/5)
  - Transcript – Wood, V. Jarvis, SR006/A106.; 41 pages. (Box-folder 1/6)
    Suffolk County Maritime Folklife Festival.
  - Transcript – Tyler, Ben, SR007/A107.; 33 pages. (Box-folder 1/7)
    East Hampton Maritime Folklife; coot shooting.
  - Transcript – Lester, Stewart and family, SR008-SR009/A108-A109.; 51 pages. (Box-folder 1/8)
  - Transcript – Lester, Stewart; Willing, Don; and Collins, John, SR010-SR011/A110-A111.; 53 pages. (Box-folder 1/9)
  - Transcript – Lester, Stewart and family., SR012-SR013/A112-A113.; 43 pages. (Box-folder 1/10)
  - Transcript – Collins, John Jr., SR015/1002.; 26 pages. (Box-folder 1/11)
    East Hampton Maritime Folklife; Sea Food Producers co-op.
  - Transcript – Semb, Andy, SR016/1003.; 70 pages. (Box-folder 1/12)
    Life history, dragging, haul seining, bunker fishing, net mending.
  - Transcript – Dellappolla, Steve, SR017/1004.; 65 pages. (Box-folder 1/13)
    Life history, Amagansett, scalloping.
  - Transcript – Knobel, Tom, SR020/1006.; 48 pages. (Box-folder 1/14)
    Life history, gill netting, etc.
  - Transcript – Miller, Milton, SR021/1007.; 45 pages. (Box-folder 1/15)
  - Transcript – Osborne, Dave and Alisha, SR022/1008.; 50 pages. (Box-folder 1/16)
    Wainscott, cod fishing.
  - Transcript – Lester, Madge and Gail; and Lester, Stewart, SR023-SR024/1009.; 74 pages. (Box-folder 1/17)
    Family home movies.
  - Transcript –Halsey, Ellen, SR025/1010.; 45 pages. (Box-folder 2/18)
  - Transcript – Vetault, Robert, SR026/1011.; 25 pages. (Box-folder 2/19)
  - Transcript – Miller, Milton, SR027/1012.; 53 pages. (Box-folder 2/20)
  - Transcript – King, Danny, SR028/1013.; 40 pages. (Box-folder 2/21)
  - Transcript – Bennett, Brentford, SR029/1014.; 30 pages. (Box-folder 2/22)
  - Transcript – Lester, Richard, SR030/1015.; 56 pages. (Box-folder 2/23)
  - Transcript – Havens, Benny, SR031/1016.; 41 pages. (Box-folder 2/24)
  - Transcript – Vorpahl, Stuart, SR032/1017.; 46 pages. (Box-folder 2/25)
  - Transcript – Zucco, Tony, SR033/1018.; 45 pages. (Box-folder 2/26)
  - Transcript – Lester, Stewart, SR038/1022.; 47 pages. (Box-folder 2/27)
    East Hampton Maritime Folklife; scalloping.
  - Transcript – Lester, Stewart, SR041-SR042/1025.; 51 pages. (Box-folder 2/28)
  - Transcript – Lester, Stewart and Ted, SR048-SR049/1030-1031.; 32 pages. (Box-folder 2/29)
  - Transcript – Lester, Stewart and Ted, SR049/1031, Side 3.; 33 pages. (Box-folder 2/30)
  - Transcript – Lester, Tom and Brown, Harold, SR050-SR051/1032-1033.; 52 pages. (Box-folder 2/31)
  - Transcript – Lester, Tom and Brown, Harold, SR051/1033, Side 3.; 25 pages. (Box-folder 2/32)
  - Transcript – Stewart, Lester and de Menil, Adelaide, SR057-SR058/1039-1040.; 67 pages. (Box-folder 2/33)
  - Transcript – Stewart, Lester and de Menil, Adelaide, SR058/1040, Side 2.; 17 pages. (Box-folder 2/34)
  - Transcript – Stewart, Lester and de Menil, Adelaide, SR058/1040, Side 3.; 37 pages. (Box-folder 2/35)
  - Transcript – Stewart, Lester and Ted, SR059/1041, Side 1.; 16 pages. (Box-folder 3/36)
    Lifting traps.
  - Transcript – Stewart, Lester and Ted, SR060/1042, Side 3.; 25 pages. (Box-folder 3/37)
  - Transcript – de Graff, Gail Lester, SR061/1043.; 39 pages. (Box-folder 3/38)
  - Transcript – Wood, V. Jarvis, SR063-SR064/1045-1046.; 36 pages. (Box-folder 3/39)
  - Transcript – Miller, Milton, SR067/1049.; 40 pages. (Box-folder 3/40)
  - Transcript – Lester, Ruth, SR069/1051.; 26 pages. (Box-folder 3/41)
  - Transcript – de Castro, Harry and Uster, Tom, SR070/1052.; 32 pages. (Box-folder 3/42)
  - Transcript – Lester, Tom and Cathy, SR072-SR073/1053-1054.; 70 pages. (Box-folder 3/43)
    Lifting eel traps.
  - Transcript – Lester, Tom and school children, SR074/1055.; 9 pages. (Box-folder 3/44)
    Eeling.
  - Transcript – Wood, V. Jarvis, SR075/1056.; 77 pages. (Box-folder 3/45)
  - Transcript – Lester, Stewart and school children from Riverhead, SR076/1057.; 7 pages. (Box-folder 3/46)
  - Transcript – Lester, Richard and children, SR077/1058.; 28 pages. (Box-folder 3/47)
  - Transcript – Lester, Tom and Whalen, Richard, SR078/1059.; 55 pages. (Box-folder 3/48)
    Northwest woods.
  - Transcript – King, Dan; Havens, Fred; Buttonow, Tom; and Olszewski, Joe, SR079/1060.; 24 pages. (Box-folder 3/49)
    Dan King’s crew.
  - Transcript – Lester, Calvin and Eames, Don Jr., SR080/1061.; 61 pages. (Box-folder 3/50)
  - Transcript – Lester, Tom, SR081/1062.; 9 pages. (Box-folder 3/51)
    East Hampton Maritime Folklife; ice stories.
  - Transcript – Leo, Arnold, SR082/1063.; 35 pages. (Box-folder 3/52)
  - Transcript – Pagliughi, Don, SR083-SR084/1064-1065.; 77 pages. (Box-folder 3/53)
  - Transcript – Miller, Mickey; Lester, Tom; and Lowen, Brad, SR085-SR086/1066-1067.; 97 pages. (Box-folder 4/54)
  - Transcript – Miller, Michael, SR087/1068.; 28 pages. (Box-folder 4/55)
    Terkel.
  - Transcript – Lester, Captain Frank, SR088/1069.; 47 pages. (Box-folder 4/56)
  - Transcript – Miller, Micahel; Lester, Tom; and Vorpahl, Stuart, SR089/1070.; 38 pages. (Box-folder 4/57)
  - Transcript – Eames, Mary and Donald Jr., SR090/1071.; 45 pages. (Box-folder 4/58)
  - Transcript – Leland, Linda, SR091/1072.; 37 pages. (Box-folder 4/59)
  - Transcript – Lester, Diane, SR092/1073.; 40 pages. (Box-folder 4/60)
  - Transcript – Duryea, Perry Jr., SR093/1074. (Box-folder 4/61)
    Montauk and Fort Pond Bay
  - Transcript – Lester, Cathy, SR094/1075.; 42 pages. (Box-folder 4/62)
  - Transcript – King, Marsha, SR095/1076.; 28 pages. (Box-folder 4/63)
  - Transcript – Lester, Tom, SR096/1077.; 30 pages. (Box-folder 4/64)
    Turtle fykes.
  - Transcript – Stern, Richard, SR097/1078.; 49 pages. (Box-folder 4/65)
  - Transcript – Lester, Al and Lowen, Brad, SR098-SR099/1079-1080.; 66 pages. (Box-folder 4/66)
  - Transcript – Erickson, John and Lester, Stewart, SR100/1081.; 60 pages. (Box-folder 4/67)
    Swordfishing.
  - Transcript – Lester, Stewart and Collins, John Jr., SR101/1082.; 5 pages. (Box-folder 4/68)
    Commercial dock.
  - Transcript – Leedham, Louis, SR 103/1083.; 33 pages. (Box-folder 4/69)
  - Transcript – Havens, Fred and Carol, SR104/1084.; 31 pages. (Box-folder 4/70)
  - Transcript – Lester, Stewart and Ted, SR105/1085.; 20 pages. (Box-folder 4/71)
  - Transcript – Edwards, Captain Jack and Carpentier, Ralph, SR106/1086.; 49 pages. (Box-folder 5/72)
  - Transcript – Ammon, Elisha, SR 107/1087.; 48 pages. (Box-folder 5/73)
    Montauk.
  - Transcript – Daniels, Albert, SR108/1088.; 39 pages. (Box-folder 5/74)
  - Transcript – Bennett, Walter, SR109/1089.; 30 pages. (Box-folder 5/75)
    Discusses taped interview of Frank Lester.
  - Transcript – Bennett, Walter, SR110/1089-b.; 37 pages. (Box-folder 5/76)
  - Transcript – Bennett, Walter, SR111/1089-c.; 45 pages. (Box-folder 5/77)
  - Transcript – Lester, Francis, SR112/1090.; 46 pages.. (Box-folder 5/78)
  - Transcript – Lester, Stewart, SR113/1091.; 34 pages. (Box-folder 5/79)
    Pin hooking porgies.
  - Transcript – Paine, Sydney and Carpentier, Ralph, SR114/1092.; 61 pages. (Box-folder 5/80)
  - Transcript – Behan, John, SR115-SR116/1093-1094.; 73 pages. (Box-folder 5/81)
    Public hearing of bass bill.
  - Transcript – Wood, Jarvis and Richard, SR117/1095.; 59 pages. (Box-folder 5/82)
  - Transcript – Lyke, Bill., SR120/1097.; 30 pages. (Box-folder 5/83)
  - Transcript – Wood, Jarvis and Lester, Tom, SR121/1098.; 19 pages. (Box-folder 5/84)
  - Transcript – Lester, Stewart., SR122/1099.; 29 pages. (Box-folder 5/85)
  - Transcript – Prohaska, Tony., SR123/1100.; 35 pages. (Box-folder 5/86)
  - Transcript – King, Doug, SR124/1101.; 27 pages. (Box-folder 5/87)
  - Transcript – Carpentier, Ralph, SR125/1102.; 15 pages. (Box-folder 5/88)
  - Transcript – Lafoe, Sally and Syversten, Jenny (nee Lester), SR126/1103.; 56 pages. (Box-folder 5/89)
  - Transcript – Miller, Milton and Mattheissen, Peter., SR127/1104.; 47 pages. (Box-folder 5/90)
  - Transcript – Syversten, Jenny (nee Lester)., SR128/1105.; 32 pages. (Box-folder 6/91)
  - Transcript – Whalen, Richard., SR129/1106.; 34 pages. (Box-folder 6/92)
  - Transcript – Miller, George Syd., SR130/1107.; 20 pages. (Box-folder 6/93)
  - Transcript – Syversten, Jenny (nee Lester) and Lafoe, Sally, SR131/1108.; 60 pages. (Box-folder 6/94)
  - Transcript – Lester, Robert, SR132/1109.; 61 pages. (Box-folder 6/95)
  - Transcript – Buttonow, Tom, SR133/1110.; 33 pages. (Box-folder 6/96)
  - Transcript – Lester, Lewis, SR134/1111.; 42 pages. (Box-folder 6/97)
  - Transcript – Eames, Don Sr., SR135/1112.; 36 pages. (Box-folder 6/98)
  - Transcript – Lester, Harry, SR136/1113.; 36 pages. (Box-folder 6/99)
  - Short Essays – Lester, Bill, 21 pages. (Box-folder 6/100)
    Three short essays: “Bill Lester, in his own words”; “Bill Lester, Bonacker”; and “Fish, in and out of water.”
  - Notecard Set (Box-folder 6/101)
    Photocopies of original notecard containers. See Box 8 for cards.
  - Notecard Set – Excerpts from interviews, 43 pages. (Box-folder 6/102)
    Photocopies of notecards created by donor.
  - Men’s Lives Exhibition – Publicity, 91 pages. (Box-folder 6/103)
    Press clippings, releases, and related material gathered by the donor.
  - Baymen’s Newsletter – 1974 to 1978 (Box-folder 6/104)
    13 issues
  - Printed ephemera, 22 pages. (Box-folder 6/105)
    Clearwater Navigator (Jan/Feb 1988); Suffolk Historian (Vol. 7, No. 1; 1982); Marine Education Leaflet No. 11, The Gulf Menhaden; and Daily Pound-Net Catch Chart.
  - Notecard Set (Box 8)
    Notecard index to oral history interviews. Lifestyle and Heritage sections include quotations from interviews. Topics indexed include: cod fishing, dragging, eeling, fishing, gill netting, hand lining, sport fishing, sword fishing, shell fishing, menhaden fishery, long lining, lobster fishing, haul seining, decoys (gunning and trapping), wind, weather and tide boats, net mending and rope splicing, whaling, trap fishing, dramatic experiences, legislation and politics, income and expenses, and shipping and selling.
- Series II: Sound Recordings
  - Original oral history interviews, SR001-SR053
  - Original oral history interviews, SR054-SR098
  - Original oral history interviews, SR099-SR146
- Series III: Graphic Images
  - Microfilm #1 – Contact Sheet (1/2), 20 pages. (Box-folder 7/106)
  - Microfilm #1 – Contact Sheet (2/2), 22 pages. (Box-folder 7/107)
  - Microfilm #2 – Contact Sheet (1/1), 16 pages. (Box-folder 7/108)
  - Microfilm #1 and Microfilm #2 (Box-folder 7/109)
    Individually boxed microfilms
Appendix A: List of Interviews
SR001/A-101 Edwards, Joshua B. and Smith, Nat. 11 July 1981
SR002/A-102 Tape not received
SR003/A-103 Smith, Nat. 14 July 1981
SR004/A-104 Edwards, Captain Jack. 12 August 1981
SR005/A-105 Edwards, Captain Jack. 12 August 1981
SR006/A-106 Tape not received
SR007/A-107 Tape not received
SR008/A-108 Tape not received
SR009/A-109 Tape not received
SR010/A-110 Lester, Stewart and Collins, Johnny. 31 August 1981
SR010/A-110 Lester, Stewart and Collins, Johnny. 31 August 1981
SR011/A-111 Tape not received
SR012/A-112 Tape not received
SR013/A-113 Tape not received
SR014/1001 Paine, Sydney. 18/[15] October 1981
SR014/1001 Paine, Sydney. 18/[15] October 1981
SR015/1002 Collins, John Jr. 21 October 1981
SR016/1003 Semb, Andy. 4 November 1981
SR017/1004 Dellapolla, Steve. 8 November 1981
SR018/1004 Dellapolla, Steve. 8 November 1981
SR019/1005 Tape not received
SR020/1006 Knobel, Tom. 3/[5] December 1981
SR021/1007 Miller, Milton. 12 December 1981
SR022/1008 Osborne, Dave and Alisha. 2 January 1982
SR023/1009 Stewart, Madge and Gail. 2 January 1982
SR024/1009 Lester, Stewart. 2 January 1981
SR025/1010 Halsey, Ellen. 6 January 1982
SR026/1011 Vetault, Robert. 13 January 1981
SR027/1012 Miller, Milton. 18 January 1981
SR028/1013 King, Danny. 27 January 1982
SR029/1014 Bennett, Brentford. 28 January 1982
SR030/1015 Lester, Richard. 28 January 1982
SR031/1016 Havens, Benny. 28 January 1982
SR032/1017 Tape not received
SR033/1018 Zucco, Tony. 10 February 1982
SR034/1019 Lester, Tom and Lowen, Brad. 15 February 1982
SR035/1020 Lester, Tom and Lowen, Brad. 15 February 1982. Tape Side 3
SR036/1021 Tape not received
SR037/1022 Lester, Tom. 28 February 1982
SR038/1022 Lester, Stewart. 4 March 1982
SR039/1023 Lester, Stewart. 4 March 1982
SR040/1024 Wood, Jarvis; Richard, Tom; and Lester, Stewart. 3 March 1982
SR041/1025 Lester, Stewart. 18 March 1982
SR042/1025 Lester, Stewart. 18 March 1982
SR043/1026 Lester, Tom. 29 March 1982
SR044/1026 Lester, Tom. 29 March 1982
SR045/1027 Lester, Tom. 12 April 1982
SR046/1028 Lester, Tom. 12 April 1982
SR047/1029 Lester, Tom. 23 April 1982
SR048/1030 Lester, Stewart and Ted. 5 Mary 1982
SR049/1031 Lester, Stewart and Ted. 5 Mary 1982
SR050/1032 Lester, Tom and Brown, Harold. 14 May 1982
SR051/1033 Lester, Tom and Brown, Harold. 14 May 1982
SR052/1034 Lester, Tom and Brown, Harold; Field, Bruce. 10 May 1982
SR053/1035 Lester, Tom, et al.
SR054/1036 Lester, Tom, et al. 16 May 1982
SR055/1037 Lester, Tom and Field, Bruce. 17 May 1982
SR056/1038 Lester, Tom, et al. 17 May 1982
SR057/1039 Lester, Stewart and de Menil, Adelaide. 22 May 1982
SR058/1040 Lester, Stewart and de Menil, Adelaide. 22 May 1982
SR059/1041 Lester, Stewart and Ted. 26 May 1982
SR060/1042 Lester, Stewart and Ted. 26 May 1982
SR061/1043 de Graff, Gail Lester. 27 May 1982
SR062/1044 Lester, Tom. 11 June 1982
SR063/1045 Wood, Jarvis. 19 June 1982
SR064/1046 Wood, Jarvis. 19 June 1982
SR065/1047 Lester, Tom. 30 June 1982
SR066/1048 Lester, Tom. 30 June 1982
SR067/1049 Miller, Milton. 22 August 1982
SR068/1050 Lester, Ruth. 8 July 1982
SR069/1051 Lester, Ruth. 15 July 1982
SR070/1052 de Castro, Harry and Uster, Tom. 28 July 1982
SR071/1052 Lester, Tom and Cathy. 27 October 1982
SR072/1053 Tape not received
SR073/1054 Lester, Tom and Cathy. 27 October 1982
SR074/1055 Lester, Tom and school children. 5 November 1982
SR075/1056 Wood, Jarvis. 5 November 1982
SR076/1057 Lester, Stewart and school children from Riverhead. 5/[8] November 1982
SR077/1058 Lester, Richard and children. 5 November 1982
SR078/1059 Lester, Tom and Whalen, Richard. 5 January 1983
SR079/1060 Havens, Fred; Buttonow, Tom; and Olszewski, Joe. 17 January 1983
SR080/1061 Lester, Calvin and Eames, Don Jr. 24 January 1983
SR081/1062 Lester, Tom. February 1983
SR082/1063 Leo, Arnold. 31 January 1983
SR083/1064 Pagliughi, Don. February 1983
SR084/1065 Pagluighi, Don. February 1983
SR085/1066 Lester, Rom; Lowen, Brad; and Miller, Mickey. 23 February 1983
SR086/1067 Lester, Tom; Lowen, Brad; and Miller, Mickey. 23 February 1983
SR087/1068 Miller, Michael. 14 February 1983
SR088/1069 Lester, Captain Frank.
SR089/1070 Miller, Michael; Lester, Tom; and Vorpahl, Stuart. 1 March 1983
SR090/1071 Eames, Mary and Donald Jr. 22 March 1983
SR091/1072 Leland, Linda. 24 March 1983
SR092/1073 Lester, Diane. 25 May 1983
SR093/1074 Duryea, Perry Jr. 29 April 1983
SR094/1075 Lester, Cathy. 29 April 1983
SR095/1076 King Marsha. 6 June 1983
SR096/1077 Lester, Tom. June 1983
SR097/1078 Stern, Richard. 19 June 1983
SR098/1079 Lester, Al and Lowen, Brad. 22 May 1983
SR099/1080 Lester, Albey and Lowen, Brad. 22 May 1983
SR100/1081 Erickson, John and Lester, Stewart. 24 June 1983
SR101/1082 Lester, Stewart and Collins, John Jr. June 1983
SR102/1083 Lester, Stewart and Collins, Johnny. 31 August 1981
SR103/1083 Leedham, Louis. 28 June 1983
SR104/1084 Havens, Fred and Carol. 22 July 1983
SR105/1085 Lester, Stewart and Ted. July 1983
SR106/1086 Tape not received
SR107/1087 Ammon, Elisha. 9 August 1983
SR108/1088 Daniels, Albert. 23 August 1983
SR109/1089 Bennett, Walter. 16 September 1983
SR110/1089-b Bennett, Walter. 17 November 1983
SR111/1089-c Bennett, Walter. 13 December 1983
SR112/1090 Lester, Francis. 20 September 1983
SR113/1091 Lester, Stewart. 3 September 1983
SR114/1092 Paine, Sydney and Carpentier, Ralph. 26 September 1983
SR115/1093 Behan, John. 3 November 1983
SR116/1094 Behan, John. 3 November 1983
SR117/1095 Wood, Jarvis and Richard. 20/[25] October 1983
SR118/1096 B., Captain Joshua; Edwards, Jack; and Carpentier, Ralph. 9 August 198[3]
SR119/1096 Public hearing at the East Hampton Town Planning Board. 30 November 1983
SR120/1097 Lyke, Bill. 12 December 1983
SR121/1098 Lester, Tom and Wood, Jarvis. 26 September 1983
SR122/1099 Lester, Stewart. 26 September 1983
SR123/1100 Prohaska, Tony. 23 December 1983
SR124/1101 Tape not received
SR125/1102 Tape not received
SR126/1103 Tape not received
SR127/1104 Miller, Milton and Mattheissen, Peter. 20 January 1984
SR128/1105 Syversten, Jenny (nee Lester). 11 February 1984
SR129/1106 Whalen, Richard. 5 March 1984
SR130/1107 Miller, George Syd. 5 March 1984
SR131/1108 Syversten, Jenny (nee Lester) and Lafoe, Sally. 14 March 1984
SR132/1109 Lester, Robert. 4 April 1984
SR133/1110 Buttonow, Tom. 9 April 1984
SR134/1111 Lester, Lewis. 10 April 1984
SR135/1112 Eames, Don Sr. 26 May 1984
SR136/1113 Lester, Harry.
SR137/1114 Stoudinger, Al and Lester, Tom.
SR138/1115 Conklin, Clifford. 27 June 1984
SR139/1116 Beckwith, Ed and Joanne. 27 June 1984
SR140 D.C. Bass meeting.
SR141 John Cronin, D.C. Bass.
SR142 Lester, Bill. 10 June 1986
SR143 Leo, Arnold and de Menil, Adelaide. 14 August 1986
SR144 de Menil, Adelaide.
SR145 East Hampton Town Marine Museum.
SR146 14 March 1976